# Nesma Manasra

FRONTEND | WEB DEVELOPER



nesmazak1999@gmil.com



+972 568062041



Github - profile - nesmamanasra



Nesma Manasrah

#### **PROFILE**

Front End Developer with over 2+ years of experience designing interfaces with frameworks and the ability to understand, analyze, develop and solve problems in various web-based applications.

Experience in converting UI/UX designs into code and designing them in a professional manner.

I have the ability to commit to work. I also have the skill to work in a large or small team and to use the tools that are handled while working in a team.

### **SKILLS**



5 HTML



**CSS** 



JavaScript



**Bootstrap** 



React



Vue



GitHub



**Firebase** 



Redux

**Problem Solving** 

**Project Management** 

## WORK EXPERIENCE

jun 2021 - sep 2021

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER REACT.JS(INTERNSHIP) Buthor co.

- Built different website interfaces using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and React.js.
- Built a Blogger website (React.js).
- Clone Amazon react.js.

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP) REMOTE

Gaza Sky Geeks

- Built different website interfaces using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and JavaScript.
- Built an E-commerce website.

# **PROJECTS**

- UI\UX to code HTML CSS JS
- Red STORE
- *→* HEADPHONES STORE
- The purpose
- → COFFEE STORE
- Delivery

### • JavaScript challenge

- shopping cart
- note app is
- Rock Paper Scissors in Gaza Sky Geek
- calculator
  - React is
- ToDo
- the blog
- Group video chat app
  - Ecommerce App

## **EDUCATION**

Sep 2017 - Jan 2020

# DIPLOMA IN WEB DEVELOPMENT AND DESIGN

Palestine Polytechnic University